MAN:
Good morning.
SHELLEY:
Hi.
This is Shelley Mayer.
I’m renting your house on Archwood Avenue.
I’m due to move in next week.
MAN:
Oh yes, hello Ms Mayer.
What can I do for you?
SHELLEY:
When I viewed the house, I told you I’ll most probably need to rent
some furniture – at least until I know whether my temporary work contract is
going to be made permanent.
MAN:
Yes of course, I remember.
And I said I could give you some information about furniture rental companies in
the city.
SHELLEY:
That’s right.
MAN:
Well, the biggest company is called Peak Rentals.
I’ve recommended them to other people and have always heard positive reports about
them.
SHELLEY:
Could you give me an idea of their costs?
MAN:
Sure, I actually have one of their brochures here.
It says the monthly price per room starts at a hundred and five dollars
and goes up to two hundred and thirty-nine dollars – that depends on which
rooms you need furniture for, of course.
SHELLEY:
Sure.
It’s just to get a general idea of how much it’s gonna
cost.
And you said you had some positive feedback about this company.
MAN:
Yes, people have mentioned that the furniture from Peak Rentals is more modern than
any of the other companies.
MAN:
And also, once you place an order, the furniture will be delivered to you in just one
or two days.
SHELLEY:
That would be really helpful.
MAN:
Oh,
and the brochure says that there’s a special offer at the moment.
MAN:
If you rent living room furniture – I believe that’s a set of chairs
and a TV table, you’ll also get a lamp at no extra cost.
SHELLEY:
OK.
But, you know,
that price range you gave is more than I was hoping to pay.
MAN:
Then you could try Aaron and Oliver.
SHELLEY:
Sorry, what and Oliver?
MAN:
Aaron.
Double-A-R-O-N.
SHELLEY:
OK.
Are they cheaper?
MAN:
I’d say they’re a mid-price company.
But if you chose them, you need to be aware that they charge an
extra twelve per cent every month in case of damage.
SHELLEY:
Oh I see.
I’d have to do the math carefully then.
MAN:
Right.
But one helpful thing is that they also do cleaning for customers.
SHELLEY:
For the furniture?
MAN:
For the house.
SHELLEY:
Oh I see.
I probably won’t need that.
MAN:
There’s another company called Larch Furniture.
It’s quite new,
and it has the lowest prices in town.
MAN:
That’s for both furniture and also electronic equipment.
SHELLEY:
Well that would be good.
I’m not bringing much with me,
and I won’t have much time to go shopping after I start my
job.
MAN:
There are two things you need to know about Larch Furniture.
First of all, you have to take out insurance on the furniture,
and you need to organise that yourself.
SHELLEY:
That wouldn’t be too hard.
MAN:
Also, you can’t take out a contract for less than six months,
but I figure that might not be a problem for you.
MAN:
You’re renting the house for twelve months after all, aren’t you?
SHELLEY:
Yes.
OK, well I …
MAN:
… sorry to interrupt.
I just thought of another furniture rental company.
It’s called Space Rentals.
And it’s located very near to the house.
SHELLEY:
OK.
MAN:
I don’t have any information about their charges,
so it’s best to use their app to find out what it would cost
you to use them.
SHELLEY:
OK thanks.
I’ll do that.
MAN:
One good thing about that company is that if you don’t like the furniture
once it’s delivered, you can request exchanges – as long as you do that
within a week of receiving it.
SHELLEY:
That sounds really great.
OK.
Well thanks very much.
That’s so helpful …